The focus is on the option mode and
guys, you can see buying
signals coming on this at this time, now just
come back from this and look at the chart, well, as soon as it comes, you will
see that it is up by two percent, some opinion
can make this controversy a great article and
if you look at the stop, the same
Redmi Double Mutton is being made,
4811 current in DJ and the skin is also showing your bread
above 1555, so hold it near Ji and the
senior officer is also of the opinion that
stoploss should be placed below 1440 and the
short term target sits between 1478 to
1498,
so this is more of an opinion for you, how should I go, it is a
matter of dot, it is coming into action, the network is
showing a good face at this time, the
mobile is also helpful in Bank of Baroda a while ago,
about which the ecology Bank
of Baroda was up by two percent a while ago
and now it is seen consolidating a bit at the upper levels
and there was
more opinion on Bank of Baroda, our opinion is very positive, Deepanshu
Bansal and I  We were discussing
whether this should be taken in the chart quarter or
else a break is
seen on the chart Kanchan I can see
around 9696, if the level of 986 is crossed then this
stock will be ready for 103 Today
banking stocks are the most bullish
and now it is the turn of Bank of Baroda,
we should buy at 98100,
okay so there will be buying above 96, this is
forming a counter for you, you have to keep an eye on the banking space,
Welspun India
also seems to have had a good start, these
images, hey look at its chart, Welspun
India is up 4%, right now you saw
a good discussion on the counter
that the opposition inspector, the formation has formed like this in the daily chart,
looking at it, it seems that it will
cross the level of 170 very soon, so from here it will be
advisable to buy from the current level, there is a
minimum target of 165 to 170 which I think is going to be
achieved very soon,
now this is a very chart, should be closed